

Enura Indula

UI/UX Engineer Cum Product Strategist

Contact

Address

Jaela, Western Province 11350

Phone

0762095125

E-mail

sri.indula@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in /enura-indula-37662815b

WWW

https://enuraindula.github.io/

Skills

Research and trend analysis

Product development

Strategic Planning

Project Management

Market Analysis

Client communication

User Interface (UI) Design

Management

User Experience (UX)

HTML & CSS

Adobe XD & Figma

methodologies

Agile development

Diligent UI/UX Engineer offering 3 years of industry success, including product roadmap development, market research, data analysis, UI development, and UX management. Highly skilled in identifying opportunities to maximize product quality and company revenue. Driven and strategic with a proven history of well - managed UI/UX engagement and product launch prowess.

Work History

TECHLEAD

2020-04 -Current

UI/UX Engineer cum Product Strategist

TechLead International PVT. LTD, Rajagiriya, Western Province

- Established criteria for each milestone within the product roadmap as means to measure developmental progress.
- Conceptualized and deployed enhanced product features and optimized implementation for use in marketing strategies.
- Coordinated design meetings and decisions across other internal departments and teams.

Monitored emerging UX design trends and practices

developments suitable for integration into future projects. Applied both qualitative and quantitative analysis techniques to continuously improve end-user

for useful techniques and cutting-edge

Managed cohesive design quality across more than five projects, adhering to prescribed themes and functional choices.

Uplabs 2018-01 -

2020-02

Uplabs Inc. Delaware Corporation, USA

UI & UX Content Creator

experiences.

Collaborated with project and product managers

- to integrate UI features complying with prescribed code standards and technical design guidelines. Developed Application Uls via emerging Ul tools
- such as Adobe XD, Figma, ProtoPie.

Education

University London 2020-02 -

2021-01

Kingston

Kingston University - London, United Kingdom

Majored in Software Engineering.

BSc. (Hons.) in Computer Science

- Coursework in Programming Patterns and
- Algorithms, Software Development Practice and Digital Entrepreneurship. **Higher National Diploma in Computing**



Pearson

2020-02

Computer Science (Pearson Assured) Esoft Metro Campus - Colombo

Awarded Most Outstanding Performer - Batch Top.

- Received a scholarship to pursue the top-up
- degree program at Kingston University, UK. Graduated with an Overall Distinction.
- International Diploma in Software

Engineering (Pearson Assured)



Pearson

Graduated with an Overall Distinction.

Esoft Metro Campus - Colombo

G.C.E Advanced Level -

2015

Mathematics Stream St. Peter's College Colombo 04 Mathematics - C

Physics - C

Chemistry - S General English - B **G.C.E Ordinary Level**



• 7As, 1B, 1C

St. Peter's College Colombo 04

Certifications

Introduction to Software Product Management -2021-02 ALBERTA University of Alberta



2020-11

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing -Google Certificate





Collaborated with a team of 15 in the development

(Available in PlayStore)



of 'The Swiss Residence' a single vendor food delivery platform. (Available in PlayStore) Collaborated with a team of 9 in the development

of 'Lankawe' a multi vendor E-Commerce Platform.

Collaborated with a team of 7 in the development



of ' E - Pasala ' a distance learning web portal for students. (Available via http:// epasala.techleadintl.com/)



Collaborated with a team of 7 in the development of 'CamTalk' a telecommunication application for Messaging, Phone Calling and Video Calling. (Available in AppStore and PlayStore)

Supervised a team of 5 junior staff members.

Affiliations



Computer Society of Sri Lanka (Affiliated by IEEE)

Student Council Member of Kingston University, UK

References (Non - Related)

Mr. Thisula Mawela

Engineering Team Techlead International PVT. LTD. Tel: +94 71 656 8744

Esoft Metro Campus Tel: +94 77 309 9297

KINGSTON

Mrs. Ama Kulathilake

Lecturer / Program Manager Degree Division (Kingston University)

Email: thisula@techleadintl.com

Business Analyst

Email: ama.k@esoft.lk

I do hereby certify that the

are true and correct to the

offered an opportunity to

company, I can assure you

that I shall always perform

duties with commitment &

loyalty.

serve in your esteemed

above particulars given by me

best of my knowledge. If I am